getmarried.com 2007-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Get Married - Wedding Planning, TV, Brides & More

The right to privacy is a core value and protected right in our country. Concerns regarding personal privacy have become even more complicated and challenging since the widespread use of the Internet for commerce purposes. With this backdrop, we want you to know that Get Married, LLC, as the owners of the getmarried.com website, are committed to protecting your right to privacy, especially as online guests of our getmarried.com website. It is our purpose in this Privacy Policy, therefore, to describe, among other things, the type of information that we gather, with whom we share such information, and how you can limit the dissemination of this information to other parties. We encourage you to carefully read this Privacy Policy and contact us at [customerservice@getmarried.com](mailto:customerservice@getmarried.com) with any questions or comments.

**Information Collection.**

We receive and may store information every time you enter the getmarried.com website or otherwise associate with our website or business in some other fashion. By way of example, we collect information when you register with us, when you call or email us, when you enter one of our sweepstakes or other contests, including, our $100,000 Wedding Giveaway, when you purchase or place an order for merchandise with us or with one of our vendors, when you enroll in one of our wedding registries, or when you elect to participate in one of our optional surveys from time to time. We may likewise receive information about you from other sources that help us to better personalize our services and product recommendations for you. The information that we collect may include, among other things, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number and additional financial information, your age, interests, product preferences, and other related demographic and marketing information. We may also gather information concerning your wedding and related events, including your bridal showers, rehearsal dinner, and honeymoon, and other information concerning those who will be participating in such events, including, their respective name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number and additional financial information.

As mentioned, we receive and may store varying types of information whenever you log onto the getmarried.com website. Like many other websites, we use cookies to obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses the getmarried.com website. “Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookie files to understand how you navigate the getmarried.com website, whether you have visited us previously, and what website or banner served as the link to the getmarried.com website. We can likewise use cookies to save and obtain your passwords and other Internet preferences. Cookies will not, however, be used to retrieve any personal information about you from your computer that you have not previously provided to us on a voluntary basis. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, please be advised that these web browsers come with an option that allows you to temporarily or permanently block their use. Please be advised that we may also use web beacons that allow us, among other things, to target our Internet ads on other websites. Web beacons are small strings of code that are placed in a web page. They are sometimes called “clear GIFs” (Graphics Interchange Format), or “pixel tags.” Additionally, for your information, we record your IP addresses and information concerning the type of operating system and browser software that you are using. This type of information assists us with our internal website administration, but may also be used for gathering certain demographic information. Finally, you should be advised that any information that is disseminated in the course of using our chat rooms, message boards, newsrooms, or the like, is public information, and specific care should be taken in not discussing or sharing information that you prefer to remain personal or private.

**Use of Information.**

We may use your information in a number of ways, including the following: (1) in order to serve you better, and improve your overall getmarried.com experience; (2) to improve the content on the getmarried.com website; (3) to exhibit content according to your preferences; (4) to inform you of important changes on our getmarried.com website, national television show, or with respect to our vendors or other business partners; (5) to send you and others marketing and promotional materials that we feel may be of interest to you, including discounts and special offers contained on the getmarried.com website, our national television show, or otherwise provided by our vendors or other business partners; or (6) if it becomes necessary to reach you. Of course, if you do not want to receive promotional e-mails or the like from us, please follow the instructions below for opting out or unsubscribing from our e-mail list.

**Shared Information.**

We use the information obtained as described above to better provide information and services to you at both the getmarried.com website and its sister national television show. We likewise share information with companies that provide support services to us, or that help market our products or services. These companies may need certain information about you in order to provide the services that we require, but they are not authorized to use the information we deliver to them for any other purposes. Additionally, we share information with vendors, business partners, and other organizations that are unrelated to Get Married, LLC, or getmarried.com. These entities may use the information that we share with them in order to provide special opportunities and offers to you, but we advise you to carefully read their respective privacy policies if their use of information is of concern to you.

Also, we may disclose your information if required to do so by law, court order, or if requested by other governmental or quasi-governmental authorities; to enforce agreements that we may have with other third-parties or to enforce the Terms and Conditions designated in the Legal Notice section of the getmarried.com website; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of the getmarried.com website, our users, or others. We may also share information that we have obtained with entities that are acquiring the getmarried.com website or merging with Get Married, LLC.

**Opt Out Procedures.**

We provide you with a number of choices regarding our handling of your personal information online and offline.

Online your choices are:

If you do not want to receive e-mail from getmarried.com, or if you do not want us to share your e-mail address and related personal information with unrelated third parties for marketing purposes, please follow the steps outlined below to submit a request electronically:

If you do not want to receive e-mail, please use the Contact Us link located at the bottom of the getmarried.com website, filling the form out completely, and typing "UNSUBSCRIBE FROM EMAIL" in the Comments area provided. (Please note that every time we send you an email, we will give you the option to unsubscribe from our e-mail list, so you'll be able to stop our e-mails at any time).

If you do not wish your e-mail address and related personal information to be shared with unrelated third parties for marketing purposes, please use the same Contact Us link, filling the form out completely, and typing "KEEP PRIVATE" in the Comments area provided.

If you wish both steps to be taken, please use the Contact Us link, filling out the form completely, but typing "NO EMAIL/KEEP PRIVATE" in the Comments area provided.

**Offline your choices are:**

If you prefer, you can contact us by telephone at 1-404-888-9091, or by writing to us at Get Married Customer Service, 1065 Spring Street, Atlanta, GA 30309. If you choose to write us, please include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and state one of the following:

"NO MAIL OFFERS" (if you do not want to receive offers by mail);

"NO PHONE OFFERS" (if you do not want to receive offers by telephone); or

"NO PHONE OR MAIL OFFERS" (if you do not want to receive either).

Since customer lists often are prepared well in advance of an offering (sometimes 3-4 months before the offer is made), you may continue to receive some offers after you send us a request not to use your information for specified marketing purposes. We appreciate your patience and understanding in giving us time to carry out your request.

You also may use the address and telephone number designated above to request that we not disclose your personal information to unrelated third parties for marketing purposes. If you choose to write to us, please include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and state "NO THIRD PARTY SHARING" in your request.

**Links to other Websites.**

Getmarried.com may contain links to websites operated by other third parties. Get Married, LLC has no control over, or responsibility for, their content, information, or activities, including security, and use of personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and terms of use of these third party websites before providing them with any of your personal information. In addition, you may have linked to getmarried.com through banner advertising or another website. In such cases, the website you linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. We likewise advise you to carefully read the privacy policies of those websites to determine their personal information collection and use practices.

**Privacy of Children.**

We recognize the particular importance of protecting privacy where children are involved. We are committed to protecting children's privacy on the Internet and we comply fully with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a child has provided our website with personally identifiable information, we ask that a parent or guardian call us at 1-404- 888-9091, or contact us at [customerservice@getmarried.com](mailto:customerservice@getmarried.com), and we will delete the information about the child from our files.

**Your Consent.**

By using the getmarried.com website, you consent to our use of personal information that is collected or submitted to us as described in this Privacy Policy. We may change or add to this Privacy Policy at any time, and we encourage you to review it periodically. We will communicate any such changes by one or more of the following methods: updating this page, notifying you by e-mail if you have registered your e-mail address with us, or in writing, as required by law.

**Order Security.**

In order to protect your online order information, getmarried.com uses Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. Because we use SSL, placing an order online at the getmarried.com website is just as safe as giving your credit card number over the telephone. When the letter “http” in the URL address change to “https,” the “s” indicates that you are in a secure area employing SSL.

**California Residents.**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information Get Married, LLC shares with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Get Married Customer Service, 1065 Spring Street, Atlanta, GA 30309 In your request, please specify that you want a "Get Married California Privacy Rights Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response.

**Access to Information.**

If you are a registered user of getmarried.com, you can update your information. If you would like to email our Customer Service Department please use the Contact Us Form and select the appropriate subject line from the drop down menu.

**Contact Us.**

Your confidence in the getmarried.com website experience is our highest priority. If you have any concerns about privacy and security that have not been answered in the above Privacy Policy, we invite you to contact us at either [customerservice@getmarried.com](mailto:customerservice@getmarried.com), or by telephone at 1-404-888-9091, and we'll do our best to answer your questions and put your mind at ease.
